Right now, while you're watching this,
an invisible war is happening inside the
order books of every major exchange.
Millions of decisions are being made in
milliseconds.
Positions are being hedged, stops are
being hunted, and whales are moving size
without leaving a footprint.
Most people think they're trading
against other people. They aren't. You
are trading against silicon. You are
trading against algorithms that don't
sleep, don't feel fear, and don't make
mistakes. In this course, we aren't just
going to learn about these systems, we
are going to build one. We are going to
move through the complete stack. First
is the brain. We're going to be wiring
Claude to Open Router for
institutional-grade model access.
Second, the eyes. We will be installing
the Hyperliquid whale tracker to see
smart money in real time and the
TradingView MCP to let Claude read your
charts directly. Third, the hands, where
we will be connecting Weeks, Alpaca, and
Interactive Brokers for multi-market
execution. Fourth, the workforce, where
we will be deploying agent frameworks
like Sim Pi, Hermes, and Open Claude.
Specialists that hunt for alpha while
you sleep. Fifth is the command center,
where we will be shipping a custom
Python bot to a 24/7 VPS and unifying
everything into a live ops dashboard. By
the time we're done, you won't be
staring at 12 browser tabs and
second-guessing your entries. You'll be
an operator. You'll wake up to a daily
alpha brief waiting in your inbox, a bot
managing your risk, and a system that
finally puts you on the right side of
the silicon war.
Let's get into it. AI is already a big
part of trading cryptocurrency. Not in
theory, not in some lab somewhere. Live,
on chain, and verifiable. There's a bot
on Polymarket with a wallet address
named sovereign2013
that turned $1 into $3.3 million using
AI. That's not a headline I made up. You
can look it up on chain right now. This
course is built on the blueprint
established by pioneers like Jake
Nesler, who let Claude code run a live
trading stack with $100,000 of real
capital. Every prompt, every drawdown,
and every winning trade was documented.
It proved a vital point. When you give
an agent a wheel, it doesn't just help
you trade, it is the trader. We are
generalizing that exact stack here, add
in three specific skills, five agent
frameworks, and Claude routines to
create a system that doesn't just
survive the market, but masters it. And
on Hyperliquid, an experiment called the
Alpha Arena, took the biggest AI models
in the world, Quinn, DeepSeek, Claude,
GPT, Grok, and Gemini, gave each of them
$10,000,
and let them trade live perpetuals
against each other. The results were not
even close. Some of these models, models
that millions of people are using right
now to make trading decisions, lost the
majority of their account in 4 days. And
one of them did the complete opposite.
AI-powered bots now account for roughly
70 to 80% of all crypto volume. If you
are still trading manually, you are not
competing with other retail traders
anymore. You are the liquidity. You are
the other side of the trade that the AI
is taking. That is not me trying to
scare you. That is just what is
happening right now. And here's the
thing, the tools that are creating this
gap are not locked behind a hedge fund.
They are not expensive. They are not
complicated. Claude costs $20 a month.
The Hyperliquid API is completely free
and public. TradingView, you probably
already have. Telegram, you already have
on your phone. The gap is not about
access. The gap is about knowing how to
put it together. This is the complete
zero-to-hero course for AI trading with
Claude. I am not going to give you
theory. I'm not going to show you a demo
that looks impressive, but falls apart
the moment you try to replicate it.
Everything I show you today, I have
built and run myself. This is what you
should expect, the exact contract for
the next 2.5 hours. Real money, every
tool. Claude plus open router, which
gives you the key for every model.
Three skills live. Wickstrader, Whale
Tracker, and TradingView MCP. Three
brokers connected. Wix, Alpaca, and
Interactive Brokers.
Polymarket plus Kalshi prediction
markets. Claude routines automating your
entire trading day. Agent PNL plus Sempy
plus Hermes plus open claw all deployed.
Custom Python bot on Hostinger running
24/7. Telegram bot in your pocket.
Custom dashboard tracking it all.
Nothing skipped. Every command on
screen. If you already code, skim. If
you don't, then we're going to open a
terminal together. Let's go. Before I
show you anything, I need to say
something that most AI trading videos
will never tell you. Because if you come
into this with the wrong expectation,
you're going to get hurt. Here is what
AI is genuinely good at. Writing code,
building backtest scaffolding,
synthesizing news from 10 different
sources into one clean summary,
sentiment analysis, reading a chart
screenshot and giving you a structured
technical breakdown, journaling your
trades and finding patterns in your own
data, risk logic, and turning a plain
English strategy ideas into working Pine
Script in under a minute. All of that
Claude does better than any human
working alone, faster, more
consistently, and without getting tired
at 2:00 in the morning. Here is what AI
is bad at. Price prediction, full stop.
Claude cannot tell you where Bitcoin is
going tomorrow. Nobody can. And any tool
that claims it can is lying to you,
replacing your judgment. The market will
always throw situations that no model
has seen before. Black swan events,
coordinated manipulation, macro shocks.
AI has no edge in those moments. You do.
And hallucinations. Claude will
occasionally state something confidently
that is completely wrong. A price that
does not exist. A ticker that is not
real. a statistic it invented. It does
not happen constantly, but it happens.
You always verify the critical data
point yourself. So, here's the one rule
I want you to carry through this entire
course. Claude is a research assistant
with execution hands, not an oracle. It
does the work faster than you can. It
catches things you would miss. It runs
while you sleep, but it does not replace
your judgment. It extends it. Keep that
in your head and everything I show you
today will make sense. Forget it and you
will eventually hand an AI your account
and wonder what happened. This course
makes you capable of executing faster,
not capable of predicting markets. Trade
small until your own P&L proves
otherwise.
Now, before we get a deep dive into the
course, here's what you need on your
desk before you start. First, a laptop
or a computer, Mac, Windows 11, or any
modern Linux distro with at least 8 GB
RAM minimum, but a 16 GB is recommended.
Any CPU from the last 5 years is fine.
Second is any reasonable internet
connection. You're not streaming, you're
making API calls. A cafe hotspot works.
Third is at least 2.5 hours of your
time. You can do it in chunks, but the
install spine that covers from modules 3
to 11 will benefit you from one
continuous block. Fourth, a credit card
for a few optional charges. Some tools
needs to be paid like $5 for OpenRouter
credit, $5 for Firecrawl hosting or VPS,
which is around $5 to $8 per month.
Railway for Send API, which is $5 per
month after 30-day trial. Everything
else is free tier. Before we dive into
the modules, let's get your digital
workspace organized. You'll want these
apps open, signed in, and ready on your
desktop. First, terminal. Any modern
terminal will do.
iTerm for Mac, Windows Terminal,
PowerShell, or your default Linux
Terminal. You'll be pasting commands
here starting from module three. Second,
browser. You'll use this to sign in to
Claude, Open Router, Polymarket, and
other essential platforms.
Third, Cursor. You'll need this code
editor to view and edit markdown
md files, Python  py files, and
dashboard HTML as the course progresses.
Fourth, phone. Keep your phone handy for
Telegram. You'll need it for the
integration steps once we start working
with BotFather.
Now, for the first module, we will talk
about foundation. Before we open the
terminal, we need to align on the mental
model. Most retail traders fail with AI
because they only use it for one thing,
asking for a strategy. That's 5% of the
capability. To win, we install AI into
all three layers of the trading system.
First is research. This is finding the
edge. We're talking about tracking
hyperliquid whales using Firecrawl to
scrape the open web for sentiment and
generating a daily alpha brief that
compresses thousands of data points into
the three things that actually matter.
Second is strategy. This is turning that
edge into rules. We use the TradingView
MCP, which gives Claude 78 specific
tools to auto-build Pine Script, run
backtests, and look for multi-timeframe
confluence.
Third is execution. This is moving
capital.
We use the Wick's Trading Assistant
skill to execute orders, use TradingView
to send commands via webhook, set
agentic risk management, and deploy
custom bots on Hostinger that stay
online 24/7. The edge isn't just one of
these, it's the connection between them.
Now, AI isn't magic, it's a force
multiplier. It gives you four specific
advantages that any retail trader can
now rent for pennies.
Reading speed. It reads 100 filings
while you read one. You can give a model
300 documents and it will return the
outliers in 30 seconds for about 25
cents. Production code. It writes
professional-grade Python. We're talking
CCXT wrappers and SQLite journals that
pass every check and run live on the
first try. Pattern recognition. Our
whale tracker can scan 33,000 wallets in
90 seconds.
It sorts every profitable trader by P&L
and sentiment while you're still
refreshing a tab. Uptime. You sleep, the
bot doesn't. Your system services and
Claude routines run forever. This is an
autonomous stack that earns while you're
offline. Now, before we get into the
tools, let me quickly demystify terms
you're going to hear constantly in this
space. Because if you do not know what
these mean, some of this is going to
feel more complicated than it actually
is. Let's define them now so we don't
slow down later. MCP, the model context
protocol. Think of it like a USB-C port
for Claude. It lets us plug in any
broker, chart, or data source. Open
router. This is our unified gateway. One
API key that gives us access to Claude,
GPT, Gemini, and DeepSeek with automatic
fallback. Claude has what Anthropic
calls skills. Think of them like apps
you install on your phone. Someone
builds a skill for hyper liquid whale
tracking. You install it. Now, Claude
can do that automatically without you
writing a single line of code. I'm going
to show you how to use these later in
the course. API, which means application
programming interface. This is the
machine readable door that connects
Claude directly to Weeks, Alpaca,
Interactive Brokers, TradingView,
everything.
VPS, your virtual private server. A
Linux box we rent for a few dollars a
month so your bot lives in the cloud,
not just on your laptop. Routines.
Anthropic's cloud-hosted tasks. You
schedule a prompt and it runs on their
infrastructure even when your laptop is
closed. Agents. Software that loops. It
plans, acts, observes, and replans.
We'll be deploying five different
frameworks including Senpai, Hermes, and
OpenClaude.
Prediction markets, places like
Polymarket and Kalshi. LLMs are
shockingly good here because they
compress massive amounts of context to
predict real-world outcomes. The skills
thesis and why this course leans heavily
on Claude skills.
Most people think prompt engineering is
the secret. It's not. A skill is a
folder. Inside is a specialized file
that teaches Claude a whole domain,
every command, every edge case, and
every safety fault. By dropping three
specific skills into the system, Claude
suddenly knows how to trade Wix perps,
track hyper liquid whales, and control
your TradingView desktop with 78
built-in tools. No manual coding
required, no prompt engineering, just
plug and play capability. These are the
LEGO bricks. Now, let's go build the
stack. Now, the second module covers the
complete AI trading stack. This is the
one-page map. Every tool, every broker,
every agent platform, and every skill.
If some name sounds unfamiliar right
now, don't worry. Every single box on
this map gets its own dedicated
installation module later. Right now, I
want you to see how the LEGO blocks fit
together. One, models plus OpenRouter.
Everything starts with a key. We use
OpenRouter because it gives us one
single API key to access over 300
models. No vendor lock-in. If Anthropic
goes down, we fall back to DeepSeek or
Quinn in 1 second. Now, Claude has three
different models, all with different
strengths for different output. First is
Claude Opus 4.7. This is the flagship of
Anthropic made for heavy strategy
design, code review, and Polymarket
analyzer reasoning. Second is Claude 4.6
Sonnet. This model will be our
workhorse. 90% of this course runs on
it. Third is Claude Haiku 4.5. This is
for the cheap labor. This is mostly used
for classifying news, triaging routines,
and classification of takes for pennies.
Other models include GPT, Gemini, and
DeepSeek. You can swap these into your
configuration at any time without
changing your routines.
This is incredibly useful for skeptic
panel reviews, where you have multiple
models critique a trade idea before you
pull the trigger. Next is Quinn and
Kimmy. These are your long context open
models. If you need to ingest a 100-page
10K filing or summarize massive log
files on a budget, these are your go-to
tools. Also, with Open Router,
you can even set your model to auto.
This tells the system to automatically
choose the cheapest, most capable model
available for the specific task you're
running. It's the ultimate way to
optimize your overhead while keeping
your Hermes and Open Claw agents running
24/7. All right, before we touch a
single terminal, you need to understand
what Claude actually is. There are three
versions you need to know about. The
first is claude.ai.
This is the browser version. Think of it
as a research assistant. You paste in a
chart screenshot, a news article, a
token contract. It reads it and gives
you a structured breakdown. No code, no
setup. Just open a tab and go.
The second is Claude Desktop with
Cowork. This is where it gets agentic.
Cowork does not just talk. It acts. It
can open apps on your computer, read and
edit files, run scheduled tasks, and
remember context across sessions.
So, it knows what you told it yesterday.
It knows your trading setup. It works in
the background while you are doing
something else. The third is Claude
Code. This is the most powerful version.
It is a command-line tool that writes,
runs, and iterates code autonomously.
This is what built the trading bots I'm
going to show you later. This is what
connects to your exchange and executes
real trades. Now, let's talk about where
the money actually moves. We connect to
three primary brokers, plus prediction
markets, plus the CCXT library for
everything else. First is Wex. This is
our primary crypto broker. It's no KYC,
offers a massive deposit bonus, and most
importantly, it has a V3 API built
specifically for AI integration. It
handles futures and spot in one account.
Second is Alpaca. This is your home for
US stocks and options. It's
commission-free and has the best Python
SDK in the game. It even has an official
MCP server for cloud desktop. Third is
Interactive Brokers. This is for the
pros. If you're trading global markets,
bonds, or CFDs, this is the requirement.
We use the IB Insync Python library for
pro-grade execution. We're also hitting
prediction markets, which is where that
$3 million bot lives I mentioned
earlier. The first one is Polymarket.
This is the global giant for
crypto-funded event betting. Kalshi,
which is the US regulated alternative
for Polymarket. PMXT.
This is a unified SDK that lets us
arbitrage between Polymarket and Kalshi.
If the same event has different prices
on Polymarket and Kalshi, the AI locks
in the profit automatically. And for
everything else, we have CCXT.
This is the universal translator for
over 100 exchanges. It's how we talk to
Binance for backtesting and BlowFin as a
low-latency backup and a Great Weeks
alternative. Finally, there's
HyperLiquid. It has a free public API
that requires no key for data reads.
This is where our whale tracker skill
pulls live data to see what the biggest
fish in the pond are doing. With this
course, you aren't just getting one bot,
you're getting five different
frameworks, where each does one thing
better than the others. Most power users
run a combination of these to cover
every corner of the market. First is
Agent P&L. This is the easiest entry
point. It's a plain English Wex
perpetuals agent. You can go from
copy-paste to live trading in under 2
minutes. It even has a public
leaderboard, so you can see how your
logic stacks up. Second is Sent by. This
is your personal trading powerhouse for
hyper liquid. It comes with 44
specialized MCP tools and is battle
tested with over $100 million in volume.
Under the hood, it's powered by Open
Claw. Third is Hermes. Developed by News
Research, this Python-based framework is
a beast with 95,000 stars on GitHub.
It's self-improving, meaning it
generates reusable skills from every
successful task. It's also your gateway
to Telegram, Discord, and Slack. Fourth
is Open Claw. This is the heavyweight of
the ecosystem with 345,000
stars.
Built on TypeScript and Node.js,
it has the broadest integration
possible, over 50 channels and 13,000
community skills via Claw Hub. Fifth is
Claude Routines. These are Anthropic's
cloud-hosted scheduled tasks. This is
how your logic stays alive and running
even when your laptop is closed. You
don't have to choose just one. We're
going to install all five and you'll
pick the combination that fits your
specific trading style. Finally, we drop
three super skills directly into your
Claude code. This is the unfair
advantage of this course. Whale Tracker,
real-time hyper liquid whale research
with zero API keys.
TradingView MCP, 78 tools that let
Claude literally control your
TradingView desktop, scanning charts and
writing Pine Script for you. We X
trading assistant that lets you execute
trades all in plain English.
Individually, these tools are powerful.
Combined, they create the daily alpha
brief, where your AI tracks the whales,
reads the charts, checks your portfolio,
and hands you the day's setups on a
silver platter. Study the map on this
page. Bookmark the labels you don't
know. Let's start plugging them in,
which is exactly what we're going to do
in the next module. In this module, we
are installing every essential tool
you'll need throughout the course. Five
installs. Five verify commands and one
project folder. This is the foundation.
Every module that follows assumes this
setup is perfectly in place. If you skip
a step here, the bots won't run, the API
won't connect, and you'll be
troubleshooting code instead of trading
markets. We're going to open five tabs
and install these in order. Let's get to
work. First is Python 3.12 or higher. Go
to python.org, click on on download
Python. Once the installer is
downloaded, a pop-up will appear. Click
on install Python and click yes to
accept the terms. If you're on Windows,
this is the most important part. Tick
the box that says add Python to path
during the install. If you miss that,
nothing else works.
If you're on Mac and have Homebrew, you
can type the install command from the
notes below instead. Second is node.js.
Get the LTS version from nodejs.org.
This is the engine for our MCP servers
and the Open Claw framework we'll deploy
later. Choose your operating system.
Since I'm using Windows, I'll select the
Windows installer. Accept the license
agreement, then click next until the
installation is complete. Third is Git.
Download it from git-scm.com.
We'll be using this to clone or copy the
trading skills and bot repositories
directly to your machine. Just accept
the default settings during the install.
Fourth is Cursor. This is our command
center. Go to cursor.com. It's an AI
native editor that allows Claude to
actually see your code files. Click on
download in the upper right corner.
Accept the agreement, then click next
until it installs. Fifth is your
terminal. If you're on Mac, use the
built-in terminal or iTerm2. On Windows,
use Windows Terminal from the Microsoft
Store, and always select the PowerShell
tab. Never use the old cmd.exe. Once you
can open PowerShell, you're done. Now,
let's create your trading AI folder.
This keeps the course clean and ensures
Claude knows exactly where to look. Open
your terminal and type the command on
the screen. Everything we build from
this point forward, every skill, every
config file, goes inside this folder.
Before we move to module four, we need
three green lights. Type these into your
terminal one by one. pi dash dash
version. This must be 3.12 or higher.
node dash version. You're looking for
V22 or higher. git dash dash version.
Anything in the 2.4 range is perfect. If
you get a command not found error for
Python on Windows, it's because you
didn't tick that add to path box. Don't
fight it, just rerun the installer. If
node isn't showing up, close your
terminal completely and reopen it to
refresh the system. If you see those
version numbers, you are officially
ready. Your computer is no longer just a
laptop. It's a high frequency
workstation. Take a breath, close your
browser tabs. In the next module, we are
installing Claude code and wiring up
your OpenRouter master key. Let's get
into it. In this module, we are
installing Claude desktop, the Claude
code CLI, and signing up for OpenRouter.
By the end of this module, you will have
one master key that points Claude at
over 300 different AI models. With
Sonnet 4.6 as your default workhorse and
Opus 4.7 for the heavy lifting. First,
go to claude.ai. I highly recommend the
pro plan for $20 a month. It unlocks
Claude code and gives you the usage caps
you need to actually trade. If you're
planning on running whale alerts and
risk checks 24/7, the max plan is the
move. Once you've picked a plan,
download Claude desktop. Keep it pinned
to your taskbar. Later in the course,
we're going to plug our MCP servers
directly into this app so Claude can see
your charts and files. Now, open that
terminal we set up in from the last
module. We are installing Claude code.
This is the command line interface where
70% of this course happens. Copy the
install command from the notes below. If
you see v2.x, you're live. Go ahead and
type Claude to run it for the first
time. It will give you a link to your
browser. Just sign in with your pro
account to authenticate. Next,
openrouter.ai. Sign up, then on the
dashboard, click on get API keys and
create a new key named trading AI
course. Copy that string starting with
SK or V1. Save it in a password manager
immediately. Never paste this key into a
public GitHub or chat room. This key is
essentially a credit card for AI models.
If you leak it, bots will drain your
credits in seconds. Go to credits and
add a minimum of $5. At our scale, that
will last you weeks of Sonnet usage.
Now, we have to tell Claude code to use
open router instead of talking to
Anthropic directly. This gives us the
fallback protection if one provider goes
down. We need to create a settings file.
In your terminal, you're going to create
a folder called .claud and a file called
settings.json.
Inside that file, you're going to paste
the configuration block from the course
notes. Replace the placeholder text with
your actual open router key. This tells
the system, use open router as the base
URL and use Sonnet 4.6 as my primary
model. Now, a quick alternative if you
want to keep things simple. If you
prefer to use direct Anthropic billing
and don't care about the multimodal
fallback, you can skip open router
entirely. It's a great fallback to keep
in your back pocket and you can always
switch between the two later as your
stack grows. Let's verify the wiring. Go
back to your terminal, enter your
trading folder and type Claude. Once
inside, ask it, "What model are you
running on?" Reply with the full model
ID. If it says Anthropic/Claude 3 Sonnet
4.6 or Opus 4.7 and via open router, you
have successfully built an AI
workstation that can think across any
model on the planet. Finally, we're
going to create a file called claude.md
in your project route. This is Claude's
persistent memory. Paste the house rules
from the notes into this file. This
ensures that every time you open Claude,
it remembers your brokers, your risk
limits, and your goal. And this is how
you execute faster and trade smarter
with Alex Carter. Now, the brain is
online. In the next module, we will
start connecting it to the exchanges.
Now, for this module, we will connect
Claude to WEX, which is our primary
crypto broker. We're using WEX because
it is built for this specific type of AI
automation. It has a V3 API that's
incredibly stable. It offers a $30,000
deposit bonus for new accounts, and it
allows you to get live in about 90
seconds with no KYC required for initial
trading.
Full transparency, we partner with WEX.
We chose them because their API doesn't
choke when an AI agent like Claude
starts firing multiple requests per
second. If for any reason WEX doesn't
work in your region, don't panic. This
entire course is CCXT compatible,
meaning you can swap WEX for Binance or
Kraken with a single line of code, and
which we will cover later on this
course. First, use the VIP link in the
notes below to sign up. Use a strong,
unique password. Verify your email and
make sure that VIP code is attached so
you qualify for the trading credits.
Before you touch the API, you must
enable two-factor authentication. Go to
account, then security, and turn on
Google Authenticator. WEX will not even
allow you to create API keys without
this. Save your backup codes offline. If
you lose your phone and your backup
codes, you'd lose the account, period.
Now, fund your wallet. Click on deposit.
I recommend using USDT via the Polygon
or TRC-20 networks. They have the lowest
fees. Once the funds land, transfer them
from your spot wallet to your futures
wallet. Our AI agents trade out of the
futures wallet by default. Never fund
more than you are comfortable losing.
Remember, most retail derivatives
accounts lose money. Start small.
Now, let's create the machine's
credentials. Go to API management and
create a new key. Label it AI trading
bot. You must tick these three boxes and
only these three. First is read, so the
AI can see your balance. Second is trade
via spot or futures,
so the AI can execute orders. Third is
IP whitelist. This is non-negotiable. If
you see a withdrawal box, never enable
it. If your API key ever leaks and
withdrawal is enabled, your funds are
gone. By whitelisting your current IP
address, you ensure that even if someone
steals your key, it physically won't
work from any other computer but yours.
Weex is going to give you three values:
an API key, an API secret, and a
passphrase. Weex shows that secret
exactly once. If you close the window
before saving it, you have to delete the
key and start over. Copy all three and
put them straight into your password
manager. Do not put them in a text file.
Do not email them to yourself. You now
have a funded account, 2FA's live, and
you have your three credentials tucked
away in a secure spot. In module eight,
we're going to drop these into Claude
and let the agent take its first look at
the markets. But first, we need to
handle your equity in global markets,
which we will cover in the next module.
Now, in this module, we're moving into
the heart of the US markets. We use
Alpaca because it is quite simply the
only broker that makes Claude-driven
trading trivial. Why Alpaca? First,
commission-free API trading. Zero fees
on US stocks and ETF. Second, the paper
trading is instant. You sign up and you
get a $100,000 fake money account with
zero KYC to start. Third, it supports
fractional shares. You can tell Claude
buy $50 of Apple and it handles the math
for the decimal shares. But the killer
feature is the official MCP server. This
drops straight into Claude desktop
giving Claude trading hands without you
writing a single line of Python. Go to
alpaca.markets and sign up. Once you
verify your email, head to your
dashboard. Look for API keys and make
sure you select paper first. Generate
your keys and copy both the key ID and
the secret key immediately. Label these
clearly in your password manager as
Alpaca paper. It is shockingly easy to
accidentally fire a live order when you
think you're on paper. Don't be that
guy. Now, we're going to give Claude
desktop its hands. We need to edit a
file called Claude desktop config.json.
In the course notes, find the Alpaca MCP
block. You're going to paste that into
your config file replacing the
placeholders with your paper API keys.
Make sure the line that says
Alpaca_paper
is set to true. Once you save that file,
restart Claude desktop completely. Quit
the app then reopen it. This is the
moment. We're going to give Claude a
plain English prompt. Claude, use Alpaca
to buy $200 of NVDA at market on the
paper account. Show me my balance first
to confirm we're on paper then place the
order. Watch what happens on your
screen. Claude will call the balance
tool, verify the Alpaca_paper flag is
true, then fire the order. If you have
your Alpaca dashboard open in a browser
tab, you'll see that order appear in
under a few seconds. From this, you can
give Claude prompts for stocks plus ETF,
fractional options, and more. You now
have a system where you can manage your
entire portfolio with natural language.
You can ask for your daily P&L, scan
options chains for next Friday, or add
Meta and Microsoft to a new AI watch
list. In module 12, we're going to take
this a step further by combining this
Alpaca data with your week's crypto
positions to create a unified daily
alpha brief. Your stock market engine is
officially online. Now, in this module
is for the more advanced traders. If you
plan on trading global markets, futures,
or forex at a professional scale, you
will eventually land at Interactive
Brokers. While retail apps are great for
getting started, IBKR is the end game
broker. It gives you one login to trade
nearly every major exchange on the
planet, from New York to Tokyo. A quick
warning, IBKR is a serious institution.
Their KYC process takes about two to
three business days for approval. If
you're watching this right now, go sign
up today. Everything else in this course
still works while you wait for approval,
and you can start on their paper trading
account immediately.
Go to interactivebrokers.com and open an
account. Choose individual. The light
version is for casual investors. Pro is
the one that gives us the API access we
need. Once you're approved and funded,
you're ready to connect the machines.
Unlike Wix or Alpaca, IBKR API requires
their desktop software to be open and
logged in on your machine. You can use
the newer IBKR desktop or the classic
Trader Workstation. For this course, I
recommend TWS. It is the battle-tested
gold standard for API. Once you're
logged into TWS, go to configuration,
then API, and then settings. Check the
box that says enable active X and socket
clients. Uncheck read-only API. We need
Claude to have trading hands. Take note
of your socket port. It should be 7497
for paper and 7496 for live. The
official IBKR API is notoriously
difficult to code from scratch. That's
why we use the IB InSync library. It's
the Python wrapper that every serious
retail algo trader actually uses. Go to
your terminal and run this. In the notes
below, you'll find a 25-line Python
script. This is the moment we bridge the
gap. We're going to run a script that
connects to your local TWS session,
identifies the Apple stock contract, and
fires a buy order for one share. Run the
script and in under 2 seconds, you'll
see the order fill inside your TWS
dashboard. What's powerful here isn't
just buying one share of Apple, it's
that with three words of code, you can
switch from stocks to S&P 500 futures or
forex pairs. You are now trading at the
same level as the hedge funds. Right
now, there isn't a native MCP for IBKR
as stable as Alpaca's, but we don't need
one. Because we've installed the
IB-InSync library, we can simply ask
Claude code to write our scripts for us
on demand. You can ask Claude, "Write a
Python script to check my open positions
and close any that have a loss of more
than 3%." Claude writes it, you run it,
and the job is done. One final rule for
your Claude.md file, always tell Claude
to default to port 7497.
Never assume you are on a live port
unless you explicitly say so. Your
professional bridge is built. You now
have the crypt engine, the stock market
engine, and the global pro tier engine
all ready to go. In this module, we are
officially moving into the execution
layer. Up until now, we've been building
the machine. Now, we're giving it its
first set of specialized skills. In this
part of the course, we are installing
the Wix trading assistant. This isn't
just a basic bot, this is a deep
integration that allows Claude to open
leveraged futures, calculate position
sizes based on risk math, and attach
stop-loss and take-profit orders, all
from a single sentence in plain English.
Open your terminal, navigate to your
trading AI folder, and launch Claude
code. We're going to give Claude its
first skill by pointing it to the
repository. Copy and paste the install
prompt from the notes. You'll watch
Claude perform a Git clone to pull the
skill into its specialized folder, read
the documentation, and summarize the
tools it just learned. Once it's done,
ask Claude, "Check if the Y Trader skill
is installed and list its tools by
category." You should see a menu of
tools covering everything from account
balance to market data and futures
execution. Now, we need to feed Claude
the Wix credentials you saved in module
5. The safest way to do this is through
your shell configuration. Tell Claude,
"Help me open my shell config file so I
can add environment variables for the
Wix skill." Claude will identify whether
you need to edit your Z S H R C on Mac
or your profile on Windows. You'll paste
in your API key, secret, and passphrase.
Once you save that file, reload your
shell, and relaunch Claude. Your machine
is now authenticated and ready to trade.
Let's test the connection. Give Claude
this prompt, "Use the Wix skill to check
my futures balance. Show equity,
available margin, and unrealized P&L."
Claude will reach out to the Wix servers
and return your real-time account data.
If you see an unauthorized error,
double-check your API secret and your IP
whitelist from module 5.
Now, the moment you've been waiting for.
We are going to execute a real
risk-managed trade with one prompt.
"Check the current Bitcoin price, then
calculate a position size for a long
where I risk exactly 2% of my portfolio
with a 3% stop loss and 10 times
leverage. Execute with SL and TP at 2.5
times my risk." Watch the terminal.
Claude doesn't just guess. It fetches
the price, checks your actual equity,
does the math to find the exact number
of contracts, fires the order, and then
attaches the stop loss and take profit
orders immediately. Keep in mind, this
is a real trade. If you just want to
watch tell Claude to do a dry run only.
The skill will show you the exact JSON
it would have sent without actually
spending a dollar. The Wick's trading
assistant is now your 24/7 execution
desk. It handles futures with up to 125
times leverage. It handles spot buying
and selling. It generates daily reports
and journals your trades. It can even
copy a setup from a screenshot. Tone,
finality.
You just went from a retail trader to an
AI augmented operator. I'll see you in
module nine where we install the whale
tracker and start hunting for alpha. In
this module, we will plug into what I
call the most valuable free data set in
all of crypto, on-chain whale activity
on hyper liquid. Here's the beauty of
this skill. No API keys, no sign-ups, no
monthly subscriptions. Just pure public
data piped directly into Claude code.
We're giving your AI the ability to look
at the smartest money in the world and
ask, "What are they holding right now?"
Hyper liquid is a decentralized exchange
where every single position is public.
Entry prices, sizes, liquidations, it's
all there. The whale tracker skill wraps
that data into functions Claude can
understand. Instead of spending hours
digging through block explorers, you
just ask in plain English, "Who is net
long Bitcoin right now?" and get an
answer in seconds. First, we need one
lightweight Python package called
requests. This is what allows the skill
to talk to the internet. Open your
terminal and run this prompt. Now, let's
install the skill. Go to this link and
click download skill. Unzip the folder.
We need to move it into your
Claude  skills directory. Copy
the commands from the notes below.
There's one for Mac and a specific
PowerShell version for Windows. Once
that folder is moved, relaunch Claude
code. You've just given your assistant a
set of on-chain eyes. Let's see it in
action. This is the moment that usually
goes viral. Drop these prompts into
Claude. What are the top 20 whale
traders doing on hyperliquid right now?
Give me their aggregate net exposure,
the three most crowded longs, and any
wallet that flipped direction in the
last 24 hours. Keep it tight. I want to
read this in 60 seconds.
Watch as Claude parses thousands of data
points, groups them by asset, and spits
out a high-signal report. You now know
exactly where the smart money is
positioned before you ever place a
trade. In the notes, I've given you
seven signature prompts to steal. These
are the exact ones I run every morning.
Use smart money versus wrecked money to
see where the winners and losers
disagree. That is often where the
asymmetric setup lives. Use the morning
alpha scan to see what happened
overnight while you were sleeping. Copy
these into your clawed.md
file under a favorites heading. That
way, they're always just one click away.
Your workflow just changed forever. No
more Twitter bias or guessing. You are
building your trade ideas on hard data.
You know what the whales hold before you
decide your own direction. But research
is only half the battle. You still need
to see the charts. I'll see you in
module 10, where we give Claude control
over your TradingView.
In this module, we will unlock the
single best skill in the entire course.
We are installing the TradingView MCP.
Up until now, Claude has been smart, but
it's been blind. It had to rely on you
to tell it what the charts look like.
With these 78 new tools, Claude stops
guessing and starts engineering. It can
now read candles directly, write and
debug Pine Script V6, run backtests, and
this is the game-changer, auto-optimize
your strategies while you go get a
coffee. What does 78 tools actually
mean? It means Claude can switch symbols
and time frames, add indicators, and
pull the full report from the strategy
tester. It doesn't just see a chart, it
sees an editable canvas. If a strategy
isn't working, Claude can iterate on the
code and retest it until it finds a
profit factor that meets your standards.
Let's get the repo onto your machine.
Open your terminal and run this prompt.
During the install, you might see a play
right prompt. Say yes and let it
install. This is the automation engine
that allows Claude to drive the browser.
Now we have to tell Claude where the
server lives. You're going to open your
.mcp.json
file in your .claude folder and merge
the block from the course notes. Make
sure you replace the absolute path with
the real location of the folder on your
computer. If you're on a Mac, just type
pwd inside the folder to get the exact
string. This tells Claude, "When I ask
for a chart, use this specific engine to
go get it." To let Claude control your
charts, we have to launch a debug
version of Chrome. The repo handles this
for you with helper scripts. If you're
on Mac, run this. If you're on Windows,
use this. This will open a new Chrome
window, log in to TradingView, and keep
this tab open. This is the bridge Claude
uses to reach into the chart. Let's see
the real power. We are going to ask
Claude to not only write a strategy, but
to brute force the best settings for us.
Claude will write a dual EMA crossover
strategy, then it will systematically
run dozens of variations, changing the
fast EMA, the slow EMA, and the ATR
multiplier. It will rank them by profit
factor and hand it you the top five
winning variants with their exact
inputs. You just did a week's worth of
manual backtesting in under 5 minutes.
You now have 78 tools at your disposal.
Your stack is complete. You have the
reasoning core, the whale tracker for
on-chain alpha, and the TradingView MCP
for technical mastery. I'll see you in
module 11, where we combine all three
into your daily alpha brief. Your agent
can now read charts and track whales,
but it's still missing one thing, the
news. To trade at a high level, your AI
needs to see what's happening on the
open web. From CoinGecko and earnings
calls to FOMC minutes and exchange blog
posts, we're using Firecrawl because it
does something incredible. It takes any
messy URL and turns it into clean,
machine-readable markdown. It strips
away the ads and the clutter, handing
Claude exactly the data it needs to make
a decision. First, head over to
firecrawl.dev.
Create a free account. The free tier is
more than enough to follow along with
this course. Grab your API key. It'll
start with FC-. Copy that key and put it
into your password manager. We are about
to wire it directly into your Claude
desktop. Open Claude desktop. Inside
this, you're going to merge the
Firecrawl block from the course notes.
Paste in your API key, save the file,
and fully quit Claude desktop. You
should now see new superpowers like
Firecrawl scrape, crawl, and search.
Claude can now officially browse the
internet. Let's prove the pipeline
works. Give Claude this prompt. Use
Firecrawl scrape on the CoinGecko
Bitcoin page and return the current
price, 24-hour volume, and the top three
exchanges. Watch how it works.
Claude doesn't just guess the price
based on its training data. It reaches
out to the live site, reads the current
numbers, and summarizes them for you in
seconds.
Firecrawl's powerful, but you have to
use it strategically.
If you need on-chain data, stick with
the whale tracker. If you need price
action, use the TradingView MCP. But if
you need news, earnings reports, or
project documentation, that's where you
call Firecrawl. Don't waste your credits
scraping static information like
Wikipedia that Claude already knows. Use
Firecrawl for live data that moves
markets. I've included three prompts in
the notes that are absolute
game-changers. Use the macro pulse to
scrape the latest Federal Reserve
statement and have Claude rate how
hawkish it sounds on a scale of 1 to 10.
Use the news digest to pull the last six
articles from a major crypto news site
and summarize only the ones that could
move the market in the next 24 hours.
Your intelligence stack is officially
complete. You have the reasoning core,
the whale tracker, the chart vision, and
now web access. In the next module, we
are going to combine all of these into
the holy grail of this course, the daily
alpha brief. This is the moment
everything you've installed starts
talking to each other. We are moving
past tools and into a system of
intelligence. The daily alpha brief is a
single master prompt that chains weeks,
the whale tracker, the TradingView MCP,
and FireCrawl into one morning briefing.
This isn't just a summary, it is the
research loop that replaces your entire
doom scroll routine. In under 2 minutes,
it tells you exactly what to watch, why
you're watching it, and what size you
should trade. Up to this point, we
focused on research. No trades fired.
That's intentional. You want your agent
to understand the market before it
touches your money.
The daily alpha brief provides four
distinct layers of truth. The macro
layer, Fed chatter and overnight news
via FireCrawl.
The on-chain layer, smart money
positioning via the whale tracker. The
technical layer, trend and support and
resistance via TradingView. The
portfolio layer, your current risk and
available margin via the week scale.
When these four talk to each other,
hallucination liquidations disappear.
I've provided the master prompt in the
notes below.
This is your daily ritual. When you
paste this into Claude code, you're
going to see a symphony of tool calling.
Claude will scrape the headlines,
aggregate whale exposure, read the
4-hour charts for Bitcoin and Solana,
and check your actual account balance.
It then synthesizes all of that into a
single trade plan. It picks the highest
conviction setup, sizes it based on your
account risk, and outputs the exact
order you need to place. We don't want
to copy-paste this every morning. We
want efficiency. Take that prompt and
drop it into your claude.md file under
the heading  daily alpha. Now,
you can just type  daily alpha in
your terminal and Claude will execute
the entire chain automatically. You've
just turned a complex multi-tool
workflow into a single keystroke. Once
you've lived with this for a week, you
can start upgrading the brief. You can
pipe the text into 11 Labs so your AI
reads the market to you while you're
making coffee. You can ask Claude to
assign a confidence score from 1 to 10
and only show you setups that are seven
or higher. You can even have Claude
append every brief to a markdown
journal, making your research fully
auditable over time. You're no longer a
retail trader guessing at the next move.
You're an operator running a
professional research desk. The stack is
live. The brief is running. In the next
section of the course, we move into
autonomous operations. I'll see you in
the next module.
Up until now, you've been the one
triggering the AI. You type the command,
Claude does the work. But the goal of
this course is to build a system of
intelligence that works while you sleep.
Enter Claude routines. This is
Anthropic's native cloud-hosted
environment. You set a cron-style
schedule, pick your tools, and Claude
runs your logic in the background. It
can email you a summary, fire an alert
to your phone, or trigger an MCP side
effect. This is the easiest way to make
your daily alpha brief completely
self-driving. Head over to this site,
log in with your pro or max account.
Keep an eye on your plan limits. As of
2026, pro users get five routine runs
per day, while max users get up to 15.
You want to budget these wisely. Don't
run a research scan every 5 minutes if
you're on a pro plan. Save them for the
high-impact moments. Let's turn your
module 12 research into a routine. We'll
set this to run every weekday at 7:30
a.m. so it hits your inbox before the
market opens. Paste this routine
setting. Paste the full master prompt
from the previous module. Now, instead
of you asking Claude for the news, the
news finds you. This routine is your
radar. We'll set it to run every 2 hours
24/7. The prompt is simple. Check the
top 20 hyperliquid wallets. Only reply
if a top 10 wallet opens a position
larger than $5 million or if a whale
flips direction on Bitcoin. Tell Claude,
if no criteria are met, reply with the
word skip. This prevents your inbox from
getting cluttered with nothing to report
emails. You only get notified when there
is actual blood in the water. This is
the most important routine you'll ever
set up. It's a safety net. Set this to
run every hour during your active
trading window. It pulls your open
positions across Weeks, Alpaca, and
Interactive Brokers. It calculates your
total open risk and checks for any
position missing a stop loss. If you've
drifted past your 2% risk limit, Claude
flags it immediately. It's the unsexy
work that keeps you in the game. So,
when do you use a routine versus a local
script? Claude routines are perfect for
read and report tasks. They require zero
infrastructure and run even if your
laptop is at the bottom of a lake.
However, if you want to run arbitrary
Python code or place complex automated
orders without a human in the loop,
you'll need a VPS. We're going to build
that pro tier setup in module 24 using
Hostinger. For now, set up your first
three routines. Let the AI start doing
the heavy lifting.
In this module, you are going to ship a
full Pine Script version 6 strategy from
plain English. We're going to add
confluence filters, draw support and
resistance automatically, and debug
those frustrating red squiggles just by
describing them out loud to Claude. We
start with a clean sheet, open your
terminal, launch Claude code, and give
it the rules for a classic trend
following setup. Claude doesn't just
write the code in a text box, it uses
the MCP to open the Pine editor on your
screen, paste the code, and compile it.
If there's an error, Claude sees it and
fixes it before it ever hands the
strategy back to you. A basic strategy
is often too noisy. We need to filter
for high probability environments. Tell
Claude to take that same strategy and
add confluence filters. We'll restrict
trades to the London and New York
sessions, ensure the daily trend is in
our favor, and crucially require a
minimum amount of volatility. Claude
will update the code and show you
side-by-side stats. You'll see exactly
how those filters affected your profit
factor and your drawdown. We aren't just
guessing that a filter works, we're
proving it with data. Claude can also
handle the visual side of the chart. We
can ask it to write an indicator that
auto detects the five strongest
horizontal levels using pivots from the
last 500 bars. Ask it to color support
green and resistance red. In seconds,
Claude writes the math, compiles the
indicator, and publishes it directly to
your live chart. You now have a
custom-built technical analysis tool
tailored to your specific style. When a
script won't compile, stop Googling the
error codes. Just copy the error message
from the bottom of your TradingView
screen and paste it into Claude. Claude
uses the MCP to read the source code,
identifies the root cause, whether it's
a version mismatch or syntax error, and
recompile the fix instantly. It's like
having a senior Pine Script developer
sitting right next to you. Before you
get excited about a backtest, run it
through the honesty filter. Sample size.
If the strategy has fewer than 100
trades, it's just noise. Cost, always
tell Claude to include commission and
slippage in the settings. Real trading
isn't free. Repainting. Ask Claude to
verify that no look-ahead indicators are
used. A strategy that knows the future
on a backtest will blow up your account
in the real world. You now have the
power to engineer an edge from scratch.
In this module, we are building your
mobile control plane. We're going to use
Telegram's BotFather, install the
official Telegram plugin for Claude, and
pair your phone. By the end of this
video, your entire trading stack, the
whales, the charts, and the brokers,
will be accessible from a single chat
window in your pocket. First, open
Telegram and search for @BotFather.
This is the official way to create bots.
Send the command  newbot. Give it
a name, something like TradingOps. Give
it a unique username that ends in the
word bot. BotFather will hand you an API
token. Copy that immediately and put it
in your password manager.
This is the key that lets Claude log
into your Telegram account. Now, go back
to your terminal and launch Claude code.
We're going to install the official
plugin using  commands. Type
plugin install telegram and then
reload-plugins.
Finally, run the configuration command
and paste in that token you just got
from BotFather. You've just successfully
linked the brain to the messenger. To
make this work, we have to relaunch
Claude with the Telegram channel
attached. This allows messages to flow
in both directions. Close your current
Claude session and run the relaunch
command from the notes. You'll see a
message in your terminal saying the
Telegram channel is active and waiting.
Now, open Telegram on your phone. Find
your new bot and hit start. Send it any
message. Claude will print a
six-character pair code in your
terminal. Paste that back into Claude to
lock the connection. Then, set the
access policy to allow list. This is
critical. It ensures that only your
paired phone can drive the agent. If
anyone else finds your bot and tries to
issue a trade, they'll be denied
instantly. Let's see what this actually
looks like in the real world. Imagine
you're out for dinner and you want a
whale flash. You just text the bot, any
top 20 wallet flips in the last 2 hours?
Claude scans the chain and text you back
in seconds. Want to check your book?
Ask, what's open on Wix right now? And
get your P&L delivered as a message. You
can even execute trades. Tell Claude,
propose a Bitcoin long. Claude will do
the math and wait. It won't fire until
you reply with the word go. This human
in the loop safety rail is what keeps
you from making accidental fat finger
trades from your pocket. You are now a
mobile first operator. You have the full
power of a professional research and
execution desk condensed into a chat
app. In the next module, we're going to
dive into advanced agentic workflows.
This is the module where the thing
actually trades. We are building the
full automated pipeline. TradingView
fires an alert, Engrock forwards it to
your local server, and Claude acts as
the final decision layer to place a risk
size order on Wix. Fully automatic,
fully auditable, no more manual entry.
Think of this like a digital relay race.
Your Pine Script fires an alert with a
JSON payload. The TradingView webhook
sends that data to your Engrock URL.
Your Flask receiver, a tiny Python
server, catches the alert and triggers
Claude. Claude, using the Wix X skill,
reads the data, applies your risk rules,
and fires the order. Consistency is
everything in automation.
We use a standardized JSON schema. It
includes the symbol, the side, the
price, and your specific risk parameters
like leverage and stop loss percentages.
Copy the schema from the notes. This is
the language your alert will speak to
Claude. We aren't going to write this
Flask server line by line. We're going
to let Claude scaffold it. Paste the
prompt from section 16.3 into your
terminal. Claude will create
tv_webhook.py.
This script does three things. It
validates the incoming alert, logs it to
a file, and then shells out to the Wix
skill to execute the trade. Notice that
we aren't bypassing Claude. Claude
remains the brain that decides exactly
how to size the position before the
order hits the exchange. TradingView
lives in the cloud, but your Flask
server lives on your laptop. To bridge
that gap, we use ngrok. In your
terminal, run ngrok http 5005.
This creates a secure tunnel from the
open web directly to your machine. Copy
that ngrok-free-app
URL.
That is now your official webhook
endpoint. Now, go to your TradingView
chart, open the strategy we built in
module 14, and click the alarm icon. In
the message box, paste your JSON
payload. In the webhook URL, paste your
new ngrok address. Set the trigger to
once per bar close. The first time your
strategy conditions are met, the whole
pipeline will fire. Do not scale this
immediately. Run your first 10 alerts on
a tiny $50 test account. Watch it place
the entry, the stop loss, and the take
profit correctly. Only once you've
audited the logs and seen it work
end-to-end, do you move to your main
book. You have just closed the loop. You
are no longer chatting with an AI. You
have built an autonomous execution
engine that responds to market data in
real time. In the next module, we're
going to look at one of the most
profitable corners of the market,
prediction markets. This is where things
get truly interesting. We are moving
beyond price action and into the world
of prediction markets. This is the home
of the legendary $3 million bot, and
today, we're building our own.
Prediction markets allow you to bet on
real-world outcomes, politics, Fed
decisions, even the weather. We're going
to use Polymarket, which runs on Polygon
using USDC and Kalshi, the US regulated
venue. We're going to build a sovereign
analyzer that uses Claude Opus 4.7 to
research the news, calculate the odds,
and stake real bets. Polymarket is the
global giant. It handles billions in
monthly volume. Because it's
decentralized and uses a central limit
order book, it has the deepest liquidity
for crypto and pop culture events.
Kalshi is the pro tier CFTC regulated
venue. It's funded in US dollars and is
the gold standard for macro events like
CPI prints and Federal Reserve meetings.
Both offer open APIs, which means Claude
can price shop between them to find the
best edge. Let's get your credentials
ready. For Polymarket, connect your
MetaMask or Coinbase wallet and fund it
with USDC on the Polygon network. You'll
need to copy your private key and your
wallet address into your .env file.
Then, install the client by running pip
install prompt. For Kalshi, complete
your KYC and fund it with USD. You'll
need to generate an RSA key pair in
their API settings. Install their SDK
with pip install prompt as well. Now,
the main event. We are going to live
build analyzer.py
using Claude code. We're telling Claude
to build a script that takes a
Polymarket URL as an input. It will
fetch the current odds, then use Claude
Opus 4.7 with the web search enabled to
find the latest news. Claude will then
return a JSON response with a yes or no
decision and a confidence score. Notice
the confidence gate. We tell the bot if
confidence is high, bet $5. If it's
medium, bet two. If it's low, skip it
entirely. This gate is what prevents
your bot from overtrading on noise. The
real alpha lives in the gaps. Polymarket
and Kalshi often list the same event,
like will the Fed cut rates in June, at
different prices. We use the PMXT
library to unify both markets. This
allows Claude to see both order books at
once. If one market is at 60 cents and
the other is at 65, your bot can buy the
cheap side and lock in a nearly
risk-free profit. Before you go live,
keep your dry run flag set to true.
Watch the logs for a few days. Arbitrage
looks pristine in a screenshot, but in
the real world, gas fees and slippage
eat your margin. You now have an agent
that understands the world as well as it
understands the charts. We have spent
this course building a deep custom
infrastructure. But sometimes you just
want to test a theory now. You want to
go from an idea in your head to a live
order on the exchange in under 120
seconds. That is what Agent PNL is for.
It is the absolute easiest way to get a
Weeks trading agent running. You write
your strategy in plain English, pick
your model, and hit start. Your bot
trades Weeks perpetuals on its own, and
its performance shows up live on a
public leaderboard. The best part? You
don't have to take anyone's word for it.
Every bot on the Agent PNL leaderboard
is verifiable directly on the WX
exchange. You aren't looking at a
photoshopped screenshot. You can click
through to the actual trade logs. It's a
level of transparency that is rare in
the world of crypto bots. Let's do a
live run. Head over to agentpnl.io,
connect your Weeks account using those
API keys we generated back in module
five. Now for the strategy, you don't
need to code, just paste your logic in
plain English. Pick your model, Claude
3.5, Sonnet is the gold standard here.
Hit start. That's it. Your bot is now
live. It's scanning the markets,
managing your risk, and its PNL is
streaming to the leaderboard in real
time. Even if you prefer building your
own custom Python bots, Agent PNL is a
massive asset for three reasons. The
benchmark, you can compare your custom
strategies against public bots running
on the same venue. The sandbox, it's the
perfect place to paper test a new idea
without setting up any of your own
servers. Social alpha, the leaderboard
is a live read on what's actually
working in the current market. If a
specific bot is crushing it, you can
study its logic and even copy trade it.
Now, let's be real about the tradeoffs.
Because this is a no-code platform, it's
less flexible than the custom Python
agents we build later in the course. If
you need 10 different data sources and a
complex MCP stack, you'll outgrow this.
Also, remember your strategy is running
on their servers, not yours. Now that
you've seen the easiest way to trade
Weeks, let's look at the powerhouse for
Hyperliquid.
If Weeks is our primary crypto home,
Hyperliquid is our primary on-chain
home. To dominate that ecosystem, you
need a specialist. Enter Senpai. Senpai
is a turnkey personal trading agent
built specifically for Hyperliquid. It
packs 44 specialized MCP tools,
persistent memory, and built-in Telegram
alerts. This system has already
processed over $100 million in volume.
Under the hood, it's powered by
OpenClaw, but today we're going to focus
on getting it live in minutes. The
easiest way to keep Senpai running 24/7
is via Railway. One, go to senpai.ai and
generate an authorization token. Two,
head over to railway.app and use the
Senpai template. Three, you'll need to
fill in six environment variables,
including your OpenRouter key and your
Hyperliquid private key. Set your
strategy parameters to a conservative 1%
risk and five times leverage while
you're testing. Once you hit deploy,
Railway builds the agent in the cloud.
You can close your laptop and Senpai
will stay on the hunt. If you prefer to
keep your keys on your own machine, you
can install the Senpai skill bundle
directly into Claude Code. Open your
terminal and clone the repository. Copy
the skills into your
specialized.claudskills
directory and relaunch Claude. You now
have the exact same 44 tools, from
opportunity scanners to wallet trackers,
available right in your local terminal.
Let's see what 44 specialized tools can
actually do. Ask Senpai to rank every
trader by ROI and consistency. It
doesn't just look at P&L, it looks at
the quality of the trading. Run the
opportunity scanner to see which assets
have smart money accelerating up the
ranks. Or go full alpha and ask Senpai
to build a copy trading strategy that
mirrors the top three traders on the
leaderboard with a 5% safety stop. You
aren't just trading against the market
anymore. You are standing on the
shoulders of the most profitable giants
in the ecosystem. Senpai also features a
weekly arena. This is where agents go
head-to-head. Every trade you make earns
you points. Two points for every dollar
volume. Even if you don't care about the
prizes, watch the arena replays. It is
the best way to see how top-tier AI
agents reason under extreme market
pressure. It's a masterclass in agentic
logic. You now have a dedicated
hyperliquid specialist. Whether it's
running in the cloud or on your desk,
you have the most advanced tools
available for on-chain trading. In the
next module, we're going to look at
Hermes, the framework that allows your
agents to learn and grow on their own.
We've built execution bots and research
assistants, but now we're installing the
professor of our stack. Hermes is an
open-source Python framework from News
Research. It has nearly 100,000 stars on
GitHub and a massive community behind
it. But for us, only one feature
matters, persistent memory.
While other agents might forget what you
talked about yesterday, Hermes remembers
your prompts, your trade history, and
your journals across every single
session. It is the most alive feeling
agent in this entire course. Let's get
Hermes onto your machine. We're going to
use the official setup script because it
handles the heavy lifting. It installs a
tool called UV for speed, creates a
virtual environment, and links their
Hermes command line interface directly
to your system. Open your terminal and
clone the repo. Run this prompt. Once
that's done, you can call Hermes from
anywhere on your machine just by typing
his name. Now, run Hermes setup. This is
where we wire the brain. Select Open
Router as your provider. Use the same
master key we generated in module 4.
Pick Claude Sonnet 4.6 as your default
model. Finally, enable the Telegram
gateway. One of Hermes' unique strengths
is its flexibility. If you don't like
Telegram, you can bridge Hermes into
Discord, Slack, or even WhatsApp. It
meets you wherever you do your work.
There are four commands you need to
know. Hermes. It drops you into a live
conversation where memory is always
active. Hermes tools. This is where you
add or remove capabilities.
Hermes gateway. This starts the bridge
to your messaging apps.
Hermes doctor. If an integration fails
or a key goes missing, run the doctor.
It's the fastest way to diagnose your
system. By default, Hermes is a standard
agent. To make it self-learning, we need
to edit the config file. Open your
config.toml
and flip persistent memory and skill
generation to true. Now, when Hermes
successfully completes a complex task
like writing a new arbitrage script, it
saves that logic as a reusable skill. It
literally gets smarter the more you use
it. You might be wondering, if I have
Claude code, why do I need Hermes? Two
reasons. First, open runtime. If
Anthropic ever hits you with rate limits
on a high volatility day, Hermes keeps
running through any of the 300 models on
Open Router. Second, the journal. Hermes
is built to store long-term trade
journals. It can look back at 6 months
of your trades and identify patterns in
your behavior that you might have
missed. You now have an agent that
doesn't just trade, it studies.
In the next module, we're going to look
at the engine behind it all, Open Claw.
We are now looking at the titan of the
ecosystem. Open Claw is the largest
open-source Claw compatible agent
runtime on the planet. As of April 2026,
it has over 360,000
stars on GitHub, a massive plugin
marketplace called ClawHub, and a
high-performance TypeScript design. But
with massive reach comes massive risk.
In March of 2026 alone, nine major
security vulnerabilities were disclosed,
including remote code execution. Even
worse, independent audits found that up
to 20% of the plugins on ClawHub are
shipping malware or credential stealers.
In this module, we're going to benefit
from this massive ecosystem while
ensuring your trading keys never leave
your machine. Open Claw is a node.js
based system. Run the install command in
your terminal, but pay attention to the
versioning. Never track the latest
version in a production environment.
That is how supply chain attacks reach
you.
Pick a known good stable version like
the one listed in the course notes and
pin it. When you run Open Claw start,
the onboarding wizard will walk you
through your Open Router keys and
messaging channels. Before you install a
single plugin, you need to understand
the threats. Threat class A is
credential theft. Agents have to read
your .env files and wallet keys to work.
A malicious plugin can stream those keys
to a remote server in milliseconds.
Threat class B is unauthorized trades. A
charting plugin that asks for exchange
permissions could drain your entire
week's account while you're asleep.
Treat Claw Hub like a dark alley
marketplace. Do not install anything
blindly. From this point forward, you
follow a strict checklist for every
plugin. Verify publishers only. Only
install plugins with the blue check
badge. Permission scrutiny. If a news
reading plugin asks for shell access, it
is a virus. Deny it. Sandbox everything.
Never run Open Claw on your main
development account. Run it as a
dedicated low privilege user on your
machine. If managing security patches
sounds like a full-time job you don't
want, use One Claw.
This is the managed our SaaS version of
the platform. The core team handles the
CVE patches and audits the plugin shelf
for you. You lose some open source
street cred, but you gain a dramatically
smaller tax surface for your money. Here
is the ultimate pro move. You don't have
to choose between security and features.
You can use Hermes, which is Python base
and safe as your brain, and use Open
Claw only as a specialist tool for
specific plugins.
By using the agent communication
protocol or ACP, you can run them side
by side. You simply allow list the
specific verified Open Claw plugins that
Hermes is allowed to talk to. This is
defense in depth. Even if an Open Claw
plugin goes rogue, it physically cannot
touch the rest of your system.
You now have the keys to the largest AI
agent library in existence, and more
importantly, you have the armor to
survive it.
In the next module, we're going to look
at advanced prompt engineering to make
these agents even sharper. Trying to get
one giant prompt to handle research,
risk, and execution is exactly how
accounts get blown up. In a real
production environment, you don't use a
generalist, you use specialists. Today,
we are separating the job into three
distinct agents. We'll use Open Claw as
the orchestrator to coordinate the plan,
and Hermes as the executor to handle the
repeatable loops. They'll talk to each
other over the ACP protocol. Together,
they form a risk guardian system that
protects your capital while you hunt for
alpha. We're building a three-person
team inside your machine, the alpha
scanner. This agent reads the chain
data, the charts, and the news. It
outputs ranked trade ideas as JSON, but
crucially, it is physically incapable of
placing an order. The risk guardian,
this is a stateless veto layer. It
checks your total risk and looks for
news blackouts like an upcoming Fed
meeting. It only has two words in its
vocabulary, approve or reject. The
execute weak signal, this agent only
listens to the guardian. If and only if
a signal is approved, it calls the weak
skill to fire the trade. For these
agents to work together, they need to
speak the same language. We use a
standardized signal JSON shape. It
contains everything, the entry, the
stop, the confidence score, and the
rationale. Because both Claude and
Hermes validate the schema before
acting, hallucinated trades are filtered
out at the door. If the data doesn't fit
the shape, the machine doesn't move. In
the course notes, I provided the system
prompts for all three. Your alpha
scanner is programmed to run every 30
minutes. Your risk guardian is the
enforcer. It rejects any trade if your
total account risk is over 6% or if
there's a major CPI report in the next
90 minutes. Your executor is the
soldier. It doesn't generate ideas, it
just follows orders that have been
stamped with a guardian approved status.
Now, where do these agents live? Open
Claude runs the alpha scanner and the
risk guardian. It's the perfect
orchestrator for pulling from Fire
Claude and TradingView. For the
guardian, we can even use a smaller
model like Haiku 4.5. It's fast, cheap,
and more than enough for logic checks.
Hermes runs the execution agent. Because
Hermes has a learning loop, it actually
gets better at hitting your fills and
managing the Weex scale the more it
trades. All three communicate over the
ACP bridge we built in module 21. This
setup allows you to fan out your signals
to multiple channels. You could have a
private Telegram for your own trades and
a public alpha feed for your community,
all driven by the same brain. You have
transitioned from a single bot to a
sovereign trading desk. Your risk is
managed, your execution is specialized,
and your research is automated. In the
next module, we're going to look at the
custom code layer, the CCXT bridge.
Agents are incredible for research and
complex decision-making. But for the
tight inner loop, the moment-to-moment
check of price just ticked, should I
move my stop? You want old-school
optimized code. In this module, we're
going to use Claude code to scaffold a
professional-grade Python bot. It will
be type tested and production ready. It
uses the Weex scale for the heavy
lifting and handles the logic gates
itself. This is the bridge between AI
creativity and software stability. Our
shopping list is built for global
access. We use CCXT, which allows you to
swap between Weex, Binance, or Kraken
with a single line of code. We include
Pydantic for data validation and Loguru
for structured logs. This ensures that
if the bot does something unexpected,
you have a clear, searchable trail of
exactly why it happened. We aren't just
creating a single file. We are building
a professional directory structure.
I provided a master prompt in the notes
that tells Claude to scaffold the entire
project. From the strategy layer to the
risk guardian and the execution wrapper.
Claude will generate the models, wire
the data fetcher, and create a makefile.
This means you don't have to remember
complex commands. You just type make
test or make run paper.
Notice that we require the bot to pass
its own unit test before we even attempt
to run it. If the risk rules aren't
working in the test, the bot won't
launch. In professional trading, safety
isn't a feature, it's the foundation.
Default paper, your bot will default to
live equals false. You have to manually
flip a toggle and set an environment
variable to risk a single dollar. The
daily kill switch, if your total loss
for the day hits 3%, the bot is
programmed to flatten all positions and
exit. It protects you from yourself. The
heartbeat, every time the loop runs, the
bot sends a one-line status to your
Telegram. If your phone goes silent, you
know immediately that something is
wrong. Once Claude finishes the
scaffold, it's time for the first run.
Move into your bot directory and run
make install, then make test. If you see
all green, you are ready for make run
paper. Let this run for at least 48
hours in paper mode. Review every single
log entry. Check every simulated fill.
Make sure the risk guardian rejected the
trades it was supposed to. Only once the
logs are boring and the math is perfect
do you even think about going live. You
now have a professional Python trading
engine. It's clean, it's fast, and it's
built to be managed by you and Claude as
a team. Now that your bot is built, we
need a place for it to live 24/7. Your
laptop is not a production environment.
If your Wi-Fi drops or your battery
dies, your bot dies with it. To trade
like a professional, your code needs to
live in a hardened data center with
99.9%
uptime.
In this module, we are moving your bot
to a Hostinger KVM
2 VPS running Ubuntu 24.04.
We are going to harden your SSH access,
lock down the firewall, and wrap your
bot in a system service so it auto
restarts if it ever crashes. Head over
to this link. I recommend the KVM 2
plan. This is more than enough to run
your bot plus multiple Claude code
sessions.
When choosing a data center, think about
latency. Set a strong root password, but
don't get too attached to it. We're
going to disable it in the next step.
The second your IP address hits the
public internet, malicious bots will
start knocking on your door. We are
going to lock it down immediately.
Create a dedicated user named trader.
Upload your SSH public key from your
laptop. Disable root login and password
authentication. By doing this, even if
someone guesses your password, they
can't get in. Only your physical laptop
carrying your unique key has the badge
required to enter the server. Finally,
enable the UFW firewall and only allow
port 22 for your secure connection. Now,
login as your new trader user, update
the system, and install the Python 3.12
runtime. You're going to get clone your
trading repository, create a fresh
virtual environment, and install your
requirements. Copy your .env file from
your laptop to the server. Now, take
that VPS public IP address and go back
to your Wix API settings. Whitelist this
specific IP. This is your final layer of
security. Your API keys will now refuse
to work from any computer on Earth
except this one specific server. We
don't want to run the bot manually in a
terminal window. We want it to be a
system service. We're going to create a
system unit file. This tells Ubuntu this
bot is a priority. If the server
reboots, start the bot. If the bot
crashes, wait 5 seconds and restart it.
Once you reload the daemon and hit
start, your bot is officially a daemon,
a background process that breathes on
its own. Now that the bot is invisible
in the background, how do you see what
it's doing? You use journalctl.
Type this. This gives you a live
streaming view of your bot's heartbeat.
Every trade, every risk check, and every
API call shows up here in real time.
Your laptop is now just a remote
control. Your bot is live in a
professional data center.
In our final module, we're going to
build the glass cockpit, the personal
trading dashboard. You've done it.
You've built the engine, the radar, the
brain, and the safety net. But, looking
at 12 different terminal windows and
browser tabs is not how a professional
operator works. You need one pane of
glass. In this final module, we are
building your live ops dashboard. We'll
start by bootstrapping a
high-performance HTML skeleton with the
Wick scale. Then, we'll fold in every
other piece of the stack from Alpaca
stocks to your whale tracker data until
you have a real-time glass cockpit for
your entire trading empire. We're going
to let Claude code do the heavy lifting
here. Use the prompt in the notes to
generate a single page dashboard. We
aren't using heavy frameworks like React
or Vue. We want speed. We're going with
vanilla JavaScript, a dark theme to
match our course aesthetic, and
JetBrains Mono for the numbers because
precision matters. This dashboard will
auto-refresh every 30 seconds, showing
your equity curve, your open positions,
and your most recent signals from the
log files. Once the skeleton is live, we
start plugging in the rest of the
course. One prompt at a time, you will
ask Claude to add an Alpaca panel for
your US stocks, add a whale pulse to see
what the smart money is doing without
leaving the page, add a heartbeat panel
that monitors your VPS. If that dot
turns red, you know your bot has
stopped. Add your send P and agent P&L
stats so you can see how your autonomous
agents are performing. You're not just
building a website, you're building a
sovereign intelligence hub. Now, where
does this live? If you want it for your
eyes only, serve it from your hosting or
VPS using Caddy and lock it behind your
IP address.
If you want a fast global URL, push it
to Netlify. If you want to turn this
into a business, you can anonymize the
data and gate the dashboard behind a
wall tier. Your proof room becomes a $29
a month subscription that sells itself.
Take a look at what has changed in your
life. You went from 12 browser tabs and
doom scrolling Twitter for entries to
one single URL. Every morning the daily
alpha brief hits your inbox while you're
still in bed. Your custom bot handles
the inner loop execution with a built-in
risk guardian. And your dashboard shows
you the results in real time. You are no
longer playing the markets. You have
engineered a professional advantage.
Your computer is now a high-frequency
workstation and your agents are your
employees. The rest of the day, the rest
of the day is yours. Congratulations.
You have completed the trading AI full
course. Now go out there and execute. A
few hours ago this was a blank laptop.
Now it is a professional grade AI
trading stack. You have the research
brain, the execution hands, the risk
guardian, three brokers, and a custom
bot running in the cloud. This is the
shortest module in the course because
the work is done. This is the one that
tells you exactly what to do tomorrow
morning. Let's look at the empire you
just built. You have Claude code dialed
in. Your Wix and Alpaca accounts are
live. Interactive Brokers is bridged.
You've installed the whale tracker, the
TradingView MCP, and your daily alpha
brief. You have cloud routines running
your research, webhooks automating your
trades, a custom bot hardened on a
hosting or VPS, and a live ops dashboard
that unifies everything. You didn't just
watch a course, you shipped a production
system. A quick moment of transparency.
Every tool in this course from Wix to
Hostinger pays me a referral when you
use my links. That's how I'm able to
keep this content high velocity and high
production. When you start shipping your
own strategies or building your own
versions of this course, you should do
the same. These are the tools we
actually use. They are the backbone of
the industry. This is the most important
part of the course. This is how your
life changes tomorrow morning. You've
successfully delegated the grunt work of
trading to the machines. If you want
everything I showed you today, every
prompt, every skill code, every setup
guide, it is all inside my private
group. Link is in the description, first
link. Everything is in there. If you
found this useful, leave a like. It
genuinely does help the channel.
Subscribe if you have not already.
The system is live. The edge is yours.
Now, go out there and execute. I'll see
you at the top of the leaderboard.
You're watching charts.
Losing sleep.
Missing setups.
While bots with no emotions take the
trades you should have taken.
Trading is math. Humans feel. That's the
whole problem. AI doesn't hesitate,
doesn't revenge trade, doesn't freeze at
the 2:00 a.m. liquidation candle. It
just executes the plan every single
time.
Inside AI Trade Edge, I give you the
full stack, autonomous trading agents,
backtested strategies, plug-and-play
templates, new tools every week. Not
theory, real agents running while you
sleep, while you're at the gym, while
everyone else is still watching YouTube
tutorials. Every week you wait, someone
with worse charts and better systems
profits. AI Trade Edge, first 100 spots,
$79.99 a month, locked in forever. After
that, the price goes up permanently.
Stop watching, start executing, trade
smarter with Alex Carter. Join now.